[{"answer": "So how do you think she looks like", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What? my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I was saying the same thing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Uh, you don't have to take a picture", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "... millions and millions ..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Would I like to come up? I would love to come up. I, I'm fighting not to. Fighting! Unfortunately I uh have to get an early start tomorrow. Gotta' get up and hit that pavemen", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't know him. I know who he is", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I know. He got the hit in game SIX. So, so then what happened", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "All right. He kissed me. Okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Between a peck and a make out", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "hello. Oh, hi. What's happening? ... what? oh um, sure, ... um, yeah, okay, uh. I'll see you then. Yeah, yeah, Bye", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "That was my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What's going on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Help him move? Move what", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I know isn't that something", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't know ... he's got some valuable antiques, He's worried they'll break something", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I don't know ... he's got some valuable antiques, He's worried they'll break something", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'M NOT DRIVING HIM TO THE AIRPORT!!", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Funny, cause I happen to be very good friends with my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Know him? Would you, uh, like to meet him", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Want any help", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I'd love to help you move", "qsentId": 22}]